http://www.asohns.org.au/home/privacy-policy

ASOHNS Journal
ASOHNS Journal - Golden Jubilee Edition (2000)
Submissions to Government and Other Groups
RACS Submission on National Framework for Regulating Cosmetic Medical and Surgical Procedures
Towards a National Approach to Neonatal Hearing Screening - Draft National Framework
ASOHNS Submission to the Senate Community Affairs Committee Inquiry into Hearing Health in Australia
Member Update - Australian Government Hearing Services Program - Clinical Pathway
ASOHNS Response to ASERNIP-S report of a Rapid Review of Upper Airway Surgery for treatment of adult sleep apnoea
Position Paper on tonsillectomy and adenotonsillectomy in children
ASOHNS response re Health Legislation (Restriction on Use of Cosmetic Surgery and Solariums for Children) Amendment Bill 2008 proposed by the Queensland State Government
Government Reports
Report on Hearing Health in Australia - Executive Summary
Response to the Senate Community Affairs References Committee Report May 2011
RACS
RACS Academy of Surgical Educators
RACS Surgical Leaders' Forum
RACS Permanent Disablement Insurance
RACS Online Library Access
RACS General Information
Scientific Presentations
Research Grants
Available Research Grants
Grant Application Forms
National Registration & Accreditation
National Registration and Accreditation Scheme
National Registration and Accreditation (update)
Archive
1
Trainees
SET Contacts
Covid-19 Resources
Overview of SET Program in OHNS
OHNS SET Program Requirements
Term Dates
RACS Examinations
Specialty specific examination (SSE)
Fellowship Examination
FEX Past Papers & Support Resources
Interactive Learning
3D movable online model of translab bone resection
Ear Nose and Throat Examination - YouTube
Scientific Presentations - ASOHNS ASM 2017
Case Studies
Podcasts (Expert Opinion)
Tutorials
2019 Robert Guerin Meeting Presentations
2018 Robert Guerin Meeting Presentations
2017 Robert Guerin Meeting Presentations
2016 Robert Guerin Meeting Presentations
2014 Robert Guerin Meeting Presentations
Trainee Meetings
Robert Guerin Research Prize
Trainee Digital File & Update Contact Details
RACS Surgeon Support Program
Assessment Guidelines
Jean Littlejohn Prize
Surgical Education and Training in Otolaryngology Head & Neck Surgery
Application & Selection
Training Regulations
Training Board
Board Members
Responsibilities
Regional Training Subcommittees
Training Post Accreditation
Dashboard
Pre 2018 Procedure Based Assessment Forms
Newsletters
ASOHNS Trainee Journal Award
Privacy Policy
Information collected
The Society may collect identifiable information such as contact details. Further, access to member only services has been made possible by using information contained in Society databases. Accordingly, we collect personal information to facilitate the granting of access to member only services.
Access to information collected
The Society will not make an attempt to identify users or their browsing activities. However, in the unlikely event of an investigation, a law enforcement agency or other government agency may exercise its legal authority to inspect our Internet Service Provider's logs, and thus gain information about users and their activities. All of the identified information that the Society has used to grant member access can be viewed and changed by members when they view their personal details.
Use and disclosure of information collected
Any information you provide will only be used for the purposes for which you have provided it. It will not be disclosed to third parties without your consent.
Cookies
This website will use cookies to manage login and logout.
Security
We endeavour to ensure the Society website is secure through the use of firewalls. Personal data is maintained under strict security and can only be accessed internally by the Society employees who have permission to do so.
Find a Surgeon directory
Information retrieved by the Find a surgeon directory on the Society website will be limited to the practice address, phone, website URL and Member-nominated Areas of Special Interest of Members who are listed.
Changes to privacy statement
The Australian Society of Otolaryngology Head and Neck Surgery reserves the right to modify or amend this privacy statement at any time, provided that those modifications or amendments comply with the Privacy Act.
Quick Links
Account Links
Home
Contact Us
News
Events
Notices
Links
